internetcalls.com 2019-05-14

# Privacy Policy

Dellmont B.V. (hereinafter referred to as "DELLMONT")   is dedicated to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how DELLMONT collects and uses your personal data. It also describes your rights towards us and how to exercise them.

By using DELLMONYS’s Services, you accept our Privacy Policy and our processing of your personal data. You also agree to DELLMONT’s use of electronic communication channels to send you information. It is important that you read and understand our Privacy Policy before using our Services.

In order to provide our Services, such as our payment methods and our customer portal, we need to process your personal data, as described below. We do this with the utmost consideration.

**Information we collect about you.**

When you use our Services, we may collect the following information, including without limitation:

  * Personal and contact information – e.g. name, billing, email address, (mobile) phone number, etc.
  * Historical information – e.g. your purchase, payment and credit acceptance history
  * Information about interaction between you and Dellmont – e.g. how you use our Services, including page response times, download errors, entry and exit methods, as well as delivery notices when we contact you.
  * Device information – e.g. the IP address, language settings, browser settings, time zone settings, operating system and platform and screen resolution.
  * Geographical information – e.g. your geographical location.

**Why we collect and use personal information.**

DELLMONT collects, uses and stores your Personal Data in accordance with applicable law and EU directives regarding the Protection of Persons and Personal Data, as modified.

DELLMONT uses your Personal Data for the provision of Services and billing purposes.

DELLMONT may use your Personal Data to improve their Services.

DELLMONT may use your Personal Data to detect misuse of its system and / or a customer account.

DELLMONT may use the Personal Data to provide you with information relating to your account.

DELLMONT may use the Personal Data for marketing purposes, unless you object to this. Thus, you may at any time and without charge, contact DELLMONT to stop any use of your Personal Data for advertising or solicitation purposes.

DELLMONT and any partner involved in providing the Services will store your Personal Data no longer than the time necessary to provide Services and, in any case, no longer than the maximum period permitted by the local laws, rules and regulations on Personal Data protection.

**Disclosure and sharing of your Personal Data**

DELLMONT ensures the confidentiality of your Personal Data and will never disclose them to third parties without your consent, apart from the partners involved in providing the Services.

However, these partners involved in providing the Services will only receive the Personal Data required to perform Services. DELLMONT and its partners are prohibited from using your Personal Data for any other purposes.

Your Personal Data can be transmitted and stored in the European Union and in Switzerland, offering an adequate level of protection.

By using the Services provided by DELLMONT, you agree that your Personal Data can be transmitted to partners in Members States of European Union or in countries providing adequate protection for the provision of the Services.

Personal Data may additionally be communicated to any employee of DELLMONT or any partner involved in providing the Services. The communication to these third parties is limited to data necessary for the performance of their tasks for the same purposes as the one of DELLMONT.

**Access to your Personal Data**

You can request free access to your Personal Data processed and stored by DELLMONT in the secure MyAccount section.

**You have the following rights:**

Right of access to your Personal Data: You have the right to ask us for confirmation on whether we are processing your Personal Data, and access to the Personal Data and related information on that processing (e.g., the purposes of the processing, or the categories of Personal Data involved).

Right to correction: You have the right to have your Personal Data corrected, as permitted by law.

Right to erasure: You have the right to ask us to delete your Personal Data, as permitted by law. This right may be exercised among other things: (i) when your Personal Data is no longer necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or otherwise processed; (ii) when you withdraw consent on which processing is based and where there is no other legal ground for processing; (iii) when you object to processing pursuant to Art. 21 (1) GDPR and there are no overriding legitimate grounds for the processing, or when you object to the processing pursuant to Art. 21 (2) GDPR; or, (iv) when your Personal Data has been unlawfully processed.

Right to restriction of processing (Art. 18 GDPR): You have the right to request the limiting of our processing under limited circumstances, including: when the accuracy of your Personal Data is contested; when the processing is unlawful and you oppose the erasure of your Personal Data and request the restriction of the use of your Personal Data instead; or when you have objected to processing pursuant to Art. 21 (1) GDPR pending the verification whether the legitimate grounds of DELLMONT override your grounds.

Right to data portability: You have the right to receive the Personal Data that you have provided to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, and you have the right to transmit that information to another controller, including to have it transmitted directly, where technically feasible.

Right to object: You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data, as permitted by law. This right is limited to processing based on Art. 6 (1) (e) or (f) GDPR, and includes profiling based on those provisions, and processing for direct marketing purposes. After which, we will no longer process your Personal Data unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing that override your interests, rights and freedoms or for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.,

**Data Retention**

We will retain your Personal Data for as long as you maintain an account or as otherwise necessary to provide you the Services. We will also retain your Personal Data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Where we no longer need to process your Personal Data for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, we will delete your Personal Data from our systems.

Where permissible, we will also delete your Personal Data upon your request, after which we may not be able to continue to provide you with the Services. Information on how to make a deletion request can be found by logging into your MyAccount.

**Security of your Personal Data**

DELLMONT uses standard security technologies and procedures to ensure the protection of your Personal Data against unauthorized access, use, disclosure or destruction.

DELLMONT takes security measures, such as technical and organizational measures against unauthorized or unlawful access to your Personal Data and against accidental loss or destruction of, or damage to your Personal Data.

Any sensitive information, such as your credit card number are protected by encryption. The encrypted communication is established using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology.

Indeed, SSL provides the secure exchange of data between two computers in order to ensure the confidentiality, integrity of exchanged information and authentication by recognition of the identity of the program, the person or company with which the Personal Data is exchanged.

**Cookies**

DELLMONT draws your attention to the fact that during the time of the connection to the "www.internetcalls.com" site, a cookie can be automatically installed.

Cookies are small text files that are stored on your device and similar technologies, with the help of which our services can be provided and data can be collected. With cookies we can save your preferences and settings; make it possible for you to register; offer interest-based ads; combat fraud; and analyze how our websites and online services perform.

We may also use web beacons to help deliver cookies and collect usage and performance data. Our websites may include web beacons and cookies from other service providers.

You have a wide range of tools to manage cookies, web beacons and similar technologies, including browser control to block and remove cookies from third-party analytics services to no longer allow data collection through web beacons and similar technologies. Your browser and other choices may affect your experiences with our products.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY NOTICE**

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy notice

This Privacy Policy was last updated 05.05.2018
